const dayElevenQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the difference between our fasting and fasting of people of scriptures?",
    options: ["Period", "Number of days", "Taking Sahur", "Iftar", "Salat"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is Janabah (Ritual Bath) compulsory after sexual intercourse without discharging semen?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the fourth pillar of Islam?",
    options: ["Sadaqa", "Salat", "Zakah", "Ramadan", "Testimony"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The reward of a Salat observed at the mosque of the Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) equals to………………………..rewards of a Salat observed in another place except Ka’bah and Masjidl Aqsa.",
    options: ["100", "1000", "10000", "100000", "1000000"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Does a wet dream while fasting vitiate fasting?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "It is not allowed to say prayer (salat) in places where the camels lie down, public baths and …..",
    options: [
      "on the field",
      "in the Ship",
      "Worshop",
      "Graveyard",
      "on hospital bed",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is it right for a wife to give out her Zakat to her husband, if her husband is among the beneficiaries of Zakat mentioned in the Quran?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Kinds of Ihraam of Hajj are Ifrad, Tamatu’n and ………?",
    options: ["Umrah", "Ifaadah", "Jamrah", "Qiran", "Marwa"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is it correct to start voluntary fasting during the day (for somebody who has not drunk or ate anything after rising of fajr (dawn) of that day?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "It is allowed for ……………………..to fast on Ayamu tashreek (3 days after Eid Adha) if he or she does not have what to slaughter.",
    options: [
      "Traveller",
      "the poor",
      "Pilgrims on the Hajj",
      "Debtors",
      "Student",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Places of Ihram for those that want to perform Hajj and Umrah are Dhul – Hulaifah, Al-Juhfa, Qam-al-Manazil, Mecca and ………",
    options: ["Muzdalifah", "Safa", "Medina", "Yalamlam", "Jeddah"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Shurut Salat (conditions of solat) are: knowledge that the time for prayer has begun; purity from major and minor impurities; covering of nakedness; facing the qiblah; and, ……………",
    options: ["Takbiratul Ihram", "Adhan", "intention", "ablution", "Iqamah"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In Salat we are to keep looking at the place of Sujud (prostration) throughout of our prayer except during Tashahud that we are to be looking at…………",
    options: [
      "the Imam",
      "the finger",
      "the sky",
      "the right side",
      "the front",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Pillars of Umrah are at Tawaf, as Sa’i and ……",
    options: ["at Tamatu’", "al Ifrad", "al Ihram", "al Qiran", "an Nusuk"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Ayaam tashreek is 3 days after ………",
    options: [
      "‘Eidil Adha",
      "‘Eidil Fitr",
      "Nisfu Sha’ban",
      "yaomul ‘Arafa",
      "both ‘Eidil Adha and ‘Eidil Fitr",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
];

export default dayElevenQuestions;
